Tufts New England Medical Center Planning Office Records UA014
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Loose photographs, 1870 -- 1976; 1960 -- 1970; UA014.001; 1.2 Linear Feet; 470 Digital Object(s)
  - View of a demolition site at Washington Street looking toward Broadway Street, 1969-02; UA014.001.DO.03378; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a demolition site with the Prudential Building in the background, 1969-02; UA014.001.DO.03379; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site at Washington Street looking toward Stuart Street, 1969-02; UA014.001.DO.03380; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a storefront area at Washington Street before demolition, 1969-02; UA014.001.DO.03381; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Drilling at a construction site in the South Cove area, 1969; UA014.001.DO.03382; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction site in the South Cove area, 1969; UA014.001.DO.03383; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Drilling at a construction site in the South Cove area, 1969; UA014.001.DO.03384; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a construction site in the South Cove area, 1969-08; UA014.001.DO.03385; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Baracades around a construction site in the South Cove area, 1969-08; UA014.001.DO.03386; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction site in the South Cove area with the Ziskind Laboratory in the background, 1969-08; UA014.001.DO.03387; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Laboratories; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Construction
  - Construction site in the South Cove area with the Hotel Bradford in the background, 1969-08; UA014.001.DO.03388; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Hotels; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Construction; Bradford Hotel
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area, 1969-08; UA014.001.DO.03389; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area with the Ziskind Laboratory in the background, 1969-08; UA014.001.DO.03390; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area near the MBTA, 1970-06; UA014.001.DO.03391; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction site in the South Cove area, 1970-06; UA014.001.DO.03392; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area near the MBTA, 1970-06; UA014.001.DO.03393; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Demolition site; Subways; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - Construction site in the South Cove area near the MBTA, 1971-05; UA014.001.DO.03394; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Subways; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Construction
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area near the MBTA, 1970-06; UA014.001.DO.03395; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Subways; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Demolition sites
  - View of a construction or demolition site near the MBTA, 1970-06; UA014.001.DO.03396; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction site in the South Cove area, 1970-06; UA014.001.DO.03397; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area near the MBTA, 1970-12; UA014.001.DO.03398; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area near the MBTA, 1970-12; UA014.001.DO.03399; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Aerial view of the South Cove area, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03400; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Aerial view of the South Cove area, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03401; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Aerial view of the South Cove area, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03402; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Aerial view of the South Cove area, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03403; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Aerial view of the South Cove area, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03404; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a construction site in the South Cove area with the Ziskind Laboratory in the background, 1971-05; UA014.001.DO.03405; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of construction workers at a site in the South Cove area, 1971-05; UA014.001.DO.03406; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; People; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Construction; Workers
  - View of a construction site near the MBTA in the South Cove area, 1970-12; UA014.001.DO.03407; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Subways; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Construction
  - Construction site in the South Cove area, 1971-05; UA014.001.DO.03408; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a construction site near the MBTA in the South Cove area, 1970-12; UA014.001.DO.03409; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction of the Tufts-New England Medical Center in the South Cove area, 1972-01; UA014.001.DO.03410; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Hospitals; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Construction; New England Medical Center
  - Artist's rendering of the Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1972-05; UA014.001.DO.03411; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Color slide; image is a copy of UI03019 (8 x 10 in. black and white photo)
    Buildings; Hospitals; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Drawings; New England Medical Center
  - Artist's rendering of the Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1972-05; UA014.001.DO.03412; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction of the Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1972-02; UA014.001.DO.03413; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction of the Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1972-01; UA014.001.DO.03414; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Coffee shop interior in the South Cove area, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03415; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Coffeehouses; Interior views; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - Coffee shop under construction in the South Cove area, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03416; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Coffeehouses; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Construction
  - Coffee shop interior in the South Cove area, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03417; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Coffee shop interior in the South Cove area, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03418; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a construction site in the South Cove area with the Ziskind Laboratory in the background, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03419; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a construction site in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03420; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a construction site in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03421; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction site in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03422; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a construction site in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03423; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction site in the South Cove area, 1970-06; UA014.001.DO.03424; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction site in the South Cove area with the Ziskind Laboratory in the background, 1970-06; UA014.001.DO.03425; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction site in the South Cove area, 1970-12; UA014.001.DO.03426; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a construction site in the South Cove area, 1970-06; UA014.001.DO.03427; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a construction site in the South Cove area, 1970-12; UA014.001.DO.03428; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction site in the South Cove area, 1970-06; UA014.001.DO.03429; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction site in the South Cove area with the Ziskind Laboratory in the background, 1971-05; UA014.001.DO.03430; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction of a building in the South Cove area with the Bradford Hotel in the foreground and the Prudential Building in the background, 1971-05; UA014.001.DO.03431; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction of a building in the South Cove area near the Hancock and Prudential Buildings and the Bradford Hotel, 1971-05; UA014.001.DO.03432; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Hotels; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Construction; John Hancock building
  - Construction of the Tufts-New England Medical Center sign on a building at Washington and Bennet Streets, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03433; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Signs; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Construction; New England Medical Center
  - Construction of the Tufts-New England Medical Center sign on the side of a building at Washington and Bennet Streets, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03434; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Tufts-New England Medical Center sign on the side of a building at Washington and Bennet Streets, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03435; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Artist's rendering of the Tufts-New England Medical Center sign at Washington and Bennet Streets, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03436; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Signs; Models (representations); Tufts New England Medical Center, records; New England Medical Center
  - Construction of the parking lot at Washington and Bennet Streets, 1968; UA014.001.DO.03437; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Parking lots; Construction
  - Hospital parking lot at the New England Medical Center, 1968; UA014.001.DO.03438; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Parking lots; Construction; New England Medical Center
  - Demolition of the Tufts-New England sign at Washington and Bennet Streets, 1968-04; UA014.001.DO.03439; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Signs; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Demolition sites; New England Medical Center
  - Demolition of the Tufts-New England Medical Center sign at Washington and Bennet Streets, 1968-04; UA014.001.DO.03440; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition of the Tufts-New England Medical Center sign at Washington and Bennet Streets, 1968-04; UA014.001.DO.03441; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition of the Tufts-New England Medical Center sign, 1968-04; UA014.001.DO.03442; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition of the Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1968-04; UA014.001.DO.03443; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition of the Tufts-New England Medical Center sign at Washington and Bennet Streets, 1968-04; UA014.001.DO.03444; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition of the Tufts-New England Medical Center sign at Washington and Bennet Streets, 1968-04; UA014.001.DO.03445; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition of the Tufts-New England Medical Center sign at Washington and Bennet Streets, 1968-04; UA014.001.DO.03446; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Paul Loffoley and a diagram of The Bow Game, 1969-03; UA014.001.DO.03447; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    People; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Loffoley, Paul
- Correspondence, 1960 -- 1973; 1960 -- 1972; UA014.002; 2.4 Linear Feet
  This series contains letters between Herman H. Fields or the Planning Office and various individuals and companies regarding the development of T-NEMC and the Planning Office. Also included are personal letters between Herman H. Fields, colleagues, and the office, including family trip itineraries.
  Originally, most correspondence was housed in four boxes with overlapping alphabetical and chronological ranges, labeled "H.H.F. 1960-1966 A to K," "H.H.F. 1961-1966 A to K," "H.H.F. 1961-1966 A to S," and "H.H.F. 1961-1966 H to T."
  The folders were re-housed and their arrangement maintained.
  In addition, files from the Subject Files series labeled 'correspondence' or containing correspondence between an individual and Herman H. Fields or the Planning Office, were moved and added to the end of the Correspondence series. Folders are arranged alphabetically (B-T) and date from 1961-1972.
  - Box "H.H.F., A-K": A, 1960 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-K": B, 1960 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-K": C, 1960 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-K": D, 1960 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-K": E-F, 1960 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-K": H-I-J, 1960 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-K": K-L, 1960 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-G": A, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00008 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-G": B, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00009 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-G": C, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00010 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-G": D, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00011 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-G": E-F, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00012 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-G": G, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00013 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-S": A, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00014 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-S": B, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00015 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-S": D, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00016 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-S": H-I-J, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00017 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-S": K-L, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00018 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-S": M, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00019 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-S": N-O, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00020 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-S": P-Q, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00021 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-S": R, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00022 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., A-S": S, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00023 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., H-T": H-I-J, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00024 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., H-T": M, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00025 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., H-T": N-O, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00026 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., H-T": R, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00027 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., H-T": S, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00028 (Box 12)
  - Box "H.H.F., H-T": T-U-V, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.012.00029 (Box 12)
  - Bok, 1970 -- 1972; UA014.002.013.00001 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Boston YMCA, 1967; UA014.002.013.00002 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Eacker, 1969 -- 1971; UA014.002.013.00003 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Ehrlich, Edward, 1969 -- 1972; UA014.002.013.00004 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Easter Seal Society, 1966; UA014.002.013.00005 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Executive Director, Dr. George Wolf, 1961 -- 1968; UA014.002.013.00006 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Gallagher, Herb, 1967 -- 1969; UA014.002.013.00007 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - General, 1965; UA014.002.013.00008 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - General, 1966; UA014.002.013.00009 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - General, 1968; UA014.002.013.00010 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - General, 1970; UA014.002.013.00011 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Kavalis, Constantine, 1970; UA014.002.013.00012 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Katz, Geneva, 1964 -- 1973; UA014.002.013.00013 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Kramer, Bernie, 1970; UA014.002.013.00014 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Letters, 1972; UA014.002.013.00015 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Memos, Maria Rupp and Kay Oppermann, 1964 -- 1966; UA014.002.013.00016 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Osdoby, Sima, 1969 -- 1970; UA014.002.013.00017 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Quarles, 1967 -- 1970; UA014.002.013.00018 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Quincy School Project Staff, 1967; UA014.002.013.00019 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - School Committee of the City of Boston, 1965; UA014.002.013.00020 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - School Committee of the City of Boston, 1966; UA014.002.013.00021 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - School Committee of the City of Boston, 1967; UA014.002.013.00022 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - School Committee of the City of Boston, 1968; UA014.002.013.00023 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1965; UA014.002.013.00024 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Tufts-New England Medical Center Planning Memoranda and Correspondence, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.002.013.00025 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1966; UA014.002.013.00026 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University (Dr. George Wolf, Jr.), 1964; UA014.002.013.00027 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University (Dr. George Wolf, Jr.), 1965; UA014.002.013.00028 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
- Audiovisual materials, 1960 -- 1985; 1963 -- 1966; UA014.003; 1.2 Linear Feet
  The Audiovisual series contains visual materials and Audograph (sound) discs, created for and by the Planning Office. Sound recordings include committee, office, and business meetings conducted by Herman H. Fields. They are recorded on Audograh discs, which are pliable blue plastic flat discs recorded from the center out and re-played on dictation machines used to record them. At this time, Tufts does not have the technology required to play these discs.
  Visual material including transparencies, photographs, and maps, generally depict architectural models and plans of T-NEMC.
  Audiovisual materials are arranged alphabetically within two sub-series: Visual Files (all labeled, mostly undated, one folder dated 1966) and Audographs (Audio files, some dated 1963 through 1966, most labeled).
  - Alternate I, II, and III Sketches, 1970 -- 1985; UA014.003.013.00029 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Floating Hospital Model, UA014.003.013.00030 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
    No Date Available
  - Housing Model Photos, 1966 -- 1967; UA014.003.013.00031 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - P.I. 10.0 Photographs, UA014.003.013.00032 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - T-NEMC Model II, UA014.003.013.00033 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Ambulatory Care - Audograph, UA014.003.013.00034 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
    audograph
  - Basic Science Committee - Audograph, UA014.003.013.00035 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Blank Records - Audograph, UA014.003.013.00036 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Capital Development Programme - Audograph, 1963-10-23; UA014.003.013.00037 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Committee on Patient Care - Audograph, UA014.003.013.00038 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Joint University and Hospital Planning Committee Meetings - Audograph, 1966; UA014.003.013.00039 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Misc., Unmarked - Audograph, UA014.003.013.00040 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Miscellaneous - Audograph, 1963; UA014.003.013.00041 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Objectives Committee - Audograph, 1964; UA014.003.013.00042 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Office Reports - Audograph, UA014.003.013.00043 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Office Staff - Audograph, 1960 -- 1963; UA014.003.013.00044 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Proger, Meetings with Dr. - Audograph, UA014.003.013.00045 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Radiology - Audograph, 1963; UA014.003.013.00046 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Selverston, Dr. B. - Audograph, 1963; UA014.003.013.00047 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Stirling, Dr. - Audograph, 1964; UA014.003.013.00048 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University Dental School - Audograph, UA014.003.013.00049 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - University Planning Committee - Audograph, 1965 -- 1966; UA014.003.013.00050 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Urban Renewal, B.R.A. - Audograph, 1963 -- 1966; UA014.003.013.00051 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Wolf, Dr. G. - Audograph, 1963; UA014.003.013.00052 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
- Publications, 1940 -- 1981; 1943 -- 1971; UA014.004; 3.6 Linear Feet
  The Publication series includes annual reports, journals, plans, proposals and other miscellaneous bound volumes published for or by the T-NEMC Planning Office. Also included are articles written by Herman H. Fields, and clippings, pamphlets and articles pertaining to T-NEMC.
  Clippings and pamphlets were placed in folders and arranged alphabetically by the publishing office. Bound publications were not arranged.
  - Boston Dispensary Pamphlets, 1959 -- 1960; UA014.004.013.00053 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Clippings - Medical Center, South Cove, Etc., 1963 -- 1968; UA014.004.013.00054 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961 -- 1968; UA014.004.013.00055 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - New England Medical Center Pamplet, UA014.004.013.00056 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1966 -- 1969; UA014.004.013.00057 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Publications: H.H. Field, P. Scher, 1966 -- 1973; UA014.004.013.00058 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Tufts New England Medical Center Pamplet, 1976; UA014.004.013.00059 (Box UA014 Shared 1)
  - Adaptive Housing for the Handicapped, Paul L. Fishman, TNEMC, 1971; UA014.004.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - Adult Patient Services, NEMC Hospitals, 1966; UA014.004.014.00002 (Box 14)
  - Annual Report, The Boston Dispensary, 1956; UA014.004.014.00003 (Box 14)
  - Annual Report, Pratt Diagnostic Clinic-New England Center Hospital, 1957 -- 1958; UA014.004.014.00004 (Box 14)
  - Annual Report, Pratt Diagnostic Clinic-New England Center Hospital, 1958 -- 1959; UA014.004.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - Annual Report, Pratt Diagnostic Clinic-New England Center Hospital, 1959 -- 1960; UA014.004.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - Annual Report, Pratt Diagnostic Clinic-New England Center Hospital, 1960 -- 1961; UA014.004.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - Annual Report, Pratt Diagnostic Clinic-New England Center Hospital, 1961 -- 1962; UA014.004.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - Annual Report, Pratt Diagnostic Clinic-New England Center Hospital, 1962 -- 1963; UA014.004.014.00009 (Box 14)
  - Annual Report, Pratt Diagnostic Clinic-New England Center Hospital, 1963 -- 1964; UA014.004.014.00010 (Box 14)
  - Annual Report, New England Medical Center Hospitals, 1964 -- 1965; UA014.004.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - Annual Report, New England Medical Center Hospitals, 1965 -- 1966; UA014.004.014.00012 (Box 14)
  - Annual Report, New England Medical Center Hospitals, 1966 -- 1967; UA014.004.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - Annual Report, New England Medical Center Hospitals, 1967 -- 1968; UA014.004.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - Annual Review, New England Medical Center Hospitals, 1980; UA014.004.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - Application for a Grant of Federal Funds for Construction of Teaching Facilities, Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1965; UA014.004.014.00016 (Box 14)
  - Application for a Grant of Federal Funds for Construction of Teaching Facilities, Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1968; UA014.004.014.00017 (Box 14)
  - Applications for Computer Graphics in Community Mental Health Planning, William Hammer and Phyllis Schmitt, TNEMC, 1969; UA014.004.014.00018 (Box 14)
  - Blueprint for the Future, Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1964; UA014.004.014.00019 (Box 14)
  - Boston and Beyond: The Economic Impact of the TNEMC, Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1973; UA014.004.014.00020 (Box 14)
  - Boston Floating Hospital Pediatric Services, New England Medical Center Hospitals, 1965; UA014.004.014.00021 (Box 14)
  - Bulletin of the New England Medical Center Vol. II No. 3, Tufts Medical School and the Pratt Diagnostic Hospital, 1940; UA014.004.014.00022 (Box 14)
  - Bulletin of the New England Medical Center Vol. III No. 3, Tufts Medical School and the Pratt Diagnostic Hospital, 1941; UA014.004.014.00023 (Box 14)
  - Bulletin of the New England Medical Center Vol. III No. 6, Tufts Medical School and the Pratt Diagnostic Hospital, 1941; UA014.004.014.00024 (Box 14)
  - Bulletin of the New England Medical Center Vol. V No. 1, Tufts Medical School and the Pratt Diagnostic Hospital, 1943; UA014.004.014.00025 (Box 14)
  - Bulletin of the Tufts-New England Medical Center Vol. V No. 2, Tufts Medical School and the Pratt Diagnostic Hospital, 1959; UA014.004.014.00026 (Box 14)
  - Bulletin of the Tufts-New England Medical Center Vol. V No. 3, Tufts Medical School and the Pratt Diagnostic Hospital, 1959; UA014.004.014.00027 (Box 14)
  - Bulletin of the Tufts-New England Medical Center Vol. VI No. 1, Tufts Medical School and the Pratt Diagnostic Hospital, 1960; UA014.004.014.00028 (Box 14)
  - Bulletin of the New England Medical Center Vol. VII No. 1, Tufts Medical School and the Pratt Diagnostic Hospital, 1945; UA014.004.014.00029 (Box 14)
  - Bulletin of the New England Medical Center Vol. VIII No. 4, Tufts Medical School and the Pratt Diagnostic Hospital, 1946; UA014.004.014.00030 (Box 14)
  - Bulletin of the New England Medical Center Vol. X No. 5, Tufts Medical School and the Pratt Diagnostic Hospital, 1948; UA014.004.014.00031 (Box 14)
  - Bulletin of the New England Medical Center Vol. XIV No. 2, Tufts Medical School and the Pratt Diagnostic Hospital, 1952; UA014.004.014.00032 (Box 14)
  - Bulletin of the New England Medical Center Vol. XV No. 4, Tufts Medical School and the Pratt Diagnostic Hospital, 1953; UA014.004.014.00033 (Box 14)